[
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🍫 Unlimited chocolate",
      "🍕 Unlimited pizza"
    ],
    "choice": "🍕 Unlimited pizza",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🎶 Always hear music",
      "🎨 Always see art"
    ],
    "choice": "🎶 Always hear music",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🐶 Talk to animals",
      "🕊️ Fly like a bird"
    ],
    "choice": "🕊️ Fly like a bird",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🐶 Talk to animals",
      "🕊️ Fly like a bird"
    ],
    "choice": "🕊️ Fly like a bird",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "💤 Sleep 12 hrs/day",
      "⚡ Never need sleep again"
    ],
    "choice": "⚡ Never need sleep again",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
      "🌊 Explore the deep sea"
    ],
    "choice": "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🐶 Talk to animals",
      "🕊️ Fly like a bird"
    ],
    "choice": "🕊️ Fly like a bird",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "💤 Sleep 12 hrs/day",
      "⚡ Never need sleep again"
    ],
    "choice": "⚡ Never need sleep again",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
      "🌊 Explore the deep sea"
    ],
    "choice": "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Blue",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Green",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Orange",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Daily Micro-Journal",
    "prompt": "Name one thing you learned today.",
    "response": "storytelling",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Daily Micro-Journal",
    "prompt": "What made you smile today?",
    "response": "good working",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Daily Micro-Journal",
    "prompt": "What made you smile today?",
    "response": "good working",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🐶 Talk to animals",
      "🕊️ Fly like a bird"
    ],
    "choice": "🕊️ Fly like a bird",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🐶 Talk to animals",
      "🕊️ Fly like a bird"
    ],
    "choice": "🕊️ Fly like a bird",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
      "🌊 Explore the deep sea"
    ],
    "choice": "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Yellow",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Daily Micro-Journal",
    "prompt": "Write one thing you want to let go of.",
    "response": "nothing",
    "date": "2025-09-20"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🎶 Always hear music",
      "🎨 Always see art"
    ],
    "choice": "🎶 Always hear music",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🍫 Unlimited chocolate",
      "🍕 Unlimited pizza"
    ],
    "choice": "🍕 Unlimited pizza",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🐶 Talk to animals",
      "🕊️ Fly like a bird"
    ],
    "choice": "🐶 Talk to animals",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
      "🌊 Explore the deep sea"
    ],
    "choice": "🌊 Explore the deep sea",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
      "🌊 Explore the deep sea"
    ],
    "choice": "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Yellow",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Daily Micro-Journal",
    "prompt": "Describe a small victory you had today.",
    "response": "woke early in the mrng",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "📚 Read minds",
      "🔮 See the future"
    ],
    "choice": "📚 Read minds",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🍫 Unlimited chocolate",
      "🍕 Unlimited pizza"
    ],
    "choice": "🍕 Unlimited pizza",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "📚 Read minds",
      "🔮 See the future"
    ],
    "choice": "🔮 See the future",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "💤 Sleep 12 hrs/day",
      "⚡ Never need sleep again"
    ],
    "choice": "💤 Sleep 12 hrs/day",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🍫 Unlimited chocolate",
      "🍕 Unlimited pizza"
    ],
    "choice": "🍕 Unlimited pizza",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🎶 Always hear music",
      "🎨 Always see art"
    ],
    "choice": "🎨 Always see art",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Red",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Daily Micro-Journal",
    "prompt": "Write one thing you want to let go of.",
    "response": "woke ealry",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Daily Micro-Journal",
    "entry": {
      "date": "2025-09-21",
      "responses": {
        "Gratitude": [
          "studying for 2 hrs",
          "my parents"
        ],
        "Wins / Achievements": [
          "completing chatbot",
          "avoiding cold drink"
        ],
        "Feelings": [
          "",
          ""
        ],
        "Self-Kindness": [
          "",
          ""
        ]
      },
      "mood": "😊"
    },
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
      "🌊 Explore the deep sea"
    ],
    "choice": "🌊 Explore the deep sea",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🐶 Talk to animals",
      "🕊 Fly like a bird"
    ],
    "choice": "🐶 Talk to animals",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🎶 Always hear music",
      "🎨 Always see art"
    ],
    "choice": "🎨 Always see art",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🐶 Talk to animals",
      "🕊 Fly like a bird"
    ],
    "choice": "🐶 Talk to animals",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Orange",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Daily Micro-Journal",
    "prompt": "Describe a small victory you had today.",
    "response": "by usinf this amazin chatbot",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🎶 Always hear music",
      "🎨 Always see art"
    ],
    "choice": "🎨 Always see art",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Yellow",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Daily Micro-Journal",
    "prompt": "What made you smile today?",
    "response": "studying",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
      "🌊 Explore the deep sea"
    ],
    "choice": "🌊 Explore the deep sea",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Green",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Daily Micro-Journal",
    "prompt": "Write one thing you want to let go of.",
    "response": "woke ealry",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "📚 Read minds",
      "🔮 See the future"
    ],
    "choice": "🔮 See the future",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
      "🌊 Explore the deep sea"
    ],
    "choice": "🌊 Explore the deep sea",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Red",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Daily Micro-Journal",
    "prompt": "Name one thing you learned today.",
    "response": "woke ealry",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Daily Micro-Journal",
    "prompt": "Write one thing you want to let go of.",
    "response": "woke ealry",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Daily Micro-Journal",
    "prompt": "Describe a small victory you had today.",
    "response": "woke ealry",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🐶 Talk to animals",
      "🕊 Fly like a bird"
    ],
    "choice": "🕊 Fly like a bird",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🎶 Always hear music",
      "🎨 Always see art"
    ],
    "choice": "🎶 Always hear music",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🐶 Talk to animals",
      "🕊 Fly like a bird"
    ],
    "choice": "🐶 Talk to animals",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "💤 Sleep 12 hrs/day",
      "⚡ Never need sleep again"
    ],
    "choice": "💤 Sleep 12 hrs/day",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Yellow",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "💤 Sleep 12 hrs/day",
      "⚡ Never need sleep again"
    ],
    "choice": "⚡ Never need sleep again",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Orange",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Blue",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🍫 Unlimited chocolate",
      "🍕 Unlimited pizza"
    ],
    "choice": "🍕 Unlimited pizza",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Blue",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Blue",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
      "🌊 Explore the deep sea"
    ],
    "choice": "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Purple",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🐶 Talk to animals",
      "🕊 Fly like a bird"
    ],
    "choice": "🕊 Fly like a bird",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Would You Rather",
    "question": [
      "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
      "🌊 Explore the deep sea"
    ],
    "choice": "🌍 Travel to space 🚀",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  },
  {
    "game": "Mood Color Match",
    "color": "Purple",
    "date": "2025-09-21"
  }
]